# **Bryn Bennett**



+64 275215835



http://laserflash.tk



bryn.t.bennett@gmail.com

#### About me —

I am a fourth-year Software Engineering student at Victoria University. Some of my other passions include: yachting, canoe polo, skiing, and gaming. As well as spending a large amount of time completing university projects I have undertaken and worked on some of my own personal projects and balance this with spending time training for national and international regattas as part of the Wellington Youth Sailing Trust Youth Scheme.

## Skills -

Angular

Firebase

**HTML** 

CSS

React

Git

Java

CSharp

## Language & Frameworks

















## Education

BE(Hons) converted to B.Sc in 2019 2016 - 2019

Majoring in Computer Science

NCEA: Level 1, 2, and 3 with Excellence 2010 - 2015 Rongotai College

Web Technology and Programming, Calculus, Physics, Chemistry,

Victoria University

Geography, English, Economics

## Work Experience

2019 - present Development Squad Coach

Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

· Coaching a group of 6 teenagers

- Setting out a season plan for the squad
- · Adapting trainings for the conditions and what the sailors will find the most beneficial

Software Development of Employment Website 2018

Pihinga

- Design and developing a job search platform for solo parents
- Managing development of the project from start to finish as part of a group of six
- Requirement gathering through client interaction
- · Balancing client wants with what is feasible with the given

2018 - present Web App Development For the Following Yacht Clubs

Tup Radford Intercollegiate Yachting Academy, Queen Charlotte Yacht Club, New Plymouth Yacht Club

• Adaptation of existing work to the requirements of a different set of clients

2017 - present Yacht & Power Boat Maintenance Technician Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- · Maintenance of small keel boats and a RIB
- · Identifying what work is most important and allocating time accordingly
- · Prioritising work around upcoming events the boats will be used in.

2017 - present Web App Development For Youth Sailing Program Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- · Researching existing tools and frameworks to help the development of a web app
- Understanding of needs and the Marine Operators Safety System (MOSS) requirements
- Identifying the benefit introducing a system would have on the trusts processes

2013 - present Junior and Adult Learn to Sail Coach

Worser Bay Boating Club

- Coaching students of all ages and skill levels
- · Tailoring sessions to the students and how they learn, prac-
- · Catering for what the student wants from the course: confidence in a boat, ability to race, just having fun

# Volunteer Work

Blind Foundation - 'Have a go sailing day'2017

2013, 2017, 2018 Wellington Marathon - Drink Stations

Wellington Marathon - Marshal 2015, 2016

# **Bryn Bennett**

+64 275215835



http://laserflash.tk



bryn.t.bennett@gmail.com

Skills ———

Angular

Firebase

HTML

CSS

React

Git

Java

---

CSharp

### Language & Frameworks















#### Awards

2018

2017	Faculty of Engineering Deans List	Victoria University
2016	Excellence Scholarship	Victoria University
2015	School Prize Digital Technologies	Rongotai College
2013 - 2015	School Honours Awards for Yachting	Rongotai College

### Other Qualifications

other Qualifications		
2018	NZTA - Advanced Driving Skills	
2017	Yachting New Zealand - Learn to Sail Coach	
2016	St John - CPR & Basic First Aid	
2013	Yachting New Zealand - Assistant Learn to Sail Coach	
Sporting	Achievements	
2019	NZ Youth Match Racing Worlds Trials - 2nd(crew of 4)	
2019	Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta (crew of 4)	

(crew of 4)
Harken International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 6th (crew of 5)

Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 2nd

- 3rd

Nesspresso Youth Match Racing - 3rd (crew of 5)

2016 Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 3rd

(crew of 4)

2016 Musto International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 5th

(crew of 5)

2016 Harken International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 6th

(crew of 5)

NZ Youth Match Racing Nationals - 1st and National Champion

(crew of 4)

Nesspresso Youth Match Racing Regatta - 1st (crew of 5)

2013 College Sport Wellington Regional Canoe Polo Champion

(team of 7)

NZ Laser 4.7 Nationals - 1st and National Champion